{
    "kind": "Unscramble",
    "questions": [
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "SBP6M1L3b.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the questions",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "program / What / watch / they / did / ? ",
                    "answer": "What program did they watch?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "the / enjoyed / Who / program / ?",
                    "answer": "Who enjoyed the program?"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "SBP6M2L6c.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the sentences about the party.",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "/ need / We'll / . / paper cups /",
                    "answer": "We'll need paper cups."
                },
                {
                    "question": "/ some / make / lemonade / . / They'll /",
                    "answer": "They'll make some lemonade"
                },
                {
                    "question": "/ favorite music / . / I'll / my / bring /",
                    "answer": "I'll bring my favorite music."
                },
                {
                    "question": "/ I'll / some / take / . / photos, too / ",
                    "answer": "I'll take some photos, too."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "SBP6M2L9a.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the sentences adding will to make questions about the future.",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "we / have / the technology to stop asteroid?",
                    "answer": "Will we have the technology to stop asteroid?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "scientists / find / dinosaur DNA in their bones?",
                    "answer": "Will scientists find dinosaur DNA in their bones?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "When / you / finish / your dinosaur project?",
                    "answer": "When will you finish your "
                },
                {
                    "question": "your project / have / a lot of pictures?",
                    "answer": "Will your project have a lot of pictures?"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "SBP6M4L17b.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the questions",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "happens / What / you / if / in the sun a lot / are / ?",
                    "answer": "What happens if you are in the sun a lot?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "get a rash / he / Does / eats / if / he / seafood?",
                    "answer": "Does he get a rash if he eats seafood?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "when / happens / What / arrive / you / late at school?",
                    "answer": "What happens when you arrive late at school?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "study / you / Do / if / have / you / next day / a quiz?",
                    "answer": "Do you study if you have a quiz next day? "
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "SBP6M4L18b.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the main clauses",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "When you play with a dog, / ears or tail / its / pull / don't",
                    "answer": "When you play with a dog, don't pull its ears or tail."
                },
                {
                    "question": "When you meet a strange cat / try to / you / shouldn't / it / touch",
                    "answer": "When you meet a strange cat, you shouldn't try to touch it. "
                },
                {
                    "question": "When you pick up a rabbit, / lift / don't / by it's ears / it",
                    "answer": "When you pick up a rabbit, don't lift it by it's ears."
                },
                {
                    "question": "if a cat is with her kittens / get / you / mustn't / too close",
                    "answer": "If a cat is with her kittens, you mustn't get too close."
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}